{
    "id": "44897eb79e09458e85c7126b81ca761e",
    "title": "Subject And Object Pronouns Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "I met .............................. at the party but ...................... didn't recognize .................",
            "description": "He is a subject pronoun him and me are object pronouns. We use subject pronouns are subjects and object pronouns as objects. ",
            "answers": [
                "him, he, me",
                "he, him, I",
                "he, him, me"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I think I have seen ...................... before.",
            "description": "Here we use her because the pronoun acts as the object of the verb have seen. ",
            "answers": [
                "she",
                "her",
                "hers"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "You shouldn't have done this to ............................",
            "description": "Here we use me because the pronoun acts as the object of the preposition to. ",
            "answers": [
                "I",
                "me",
                "we"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Where could ..................................... have gone at this hour of the night?",
            "description": "We use 'she' here because the pronoun acts as the subject of the verb. ",
            "answers": [
                "she",
                "her",
                "hers"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "He took .......................... with .......................",
            "description": "Here them is the object of the verb took and him is the object of the preposition with. ",
            "answers": [
                "them, him",
                "they, he",
                "them, he"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "What is ............................ doing there?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "she",
                "her",
                "hers"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Why don't you listen to ...........................?",
            "description": "Here them is the object of the preposition to. ",
            "answers": [
                "they",
                "them",
                "their"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "No one would have done this except ........................",
            "description": "Here him acts as the object of the preposition except. ",
            "answers": [
                "he",
                "him",
                "his"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Did anyone see ...........................?",
            "description": "Here him is the object of the verb see. ",
            "answers": [
                "he",
                "him",
                "his"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "All of .............................. arrived on time.",
            "description": "Here them is the object of the preposition of. ",
            "answers": [
                "they",
                "them"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "She is taller than ...........................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "I am",
                "me",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "I saw you and ............................ there.",
            "description": "Here the pronouns you and her are the objects of the verb saw. ",
            "answers": [
                "she",
                "her",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        }
    ]
}